<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[thefrvrplaylist]]></title><description><![CDATA[Written and curated by Martin Manasherob, professionally known as mvrtinfrvr, a singer/songwriter, record producer, and audio engineer from the Bay Area, California.]]></description><link>https://thefrvrplaylist.com</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:44:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[the intro about nothing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Welcome to thefrvrplaylist! My name is Martin, and for several years now...]]></description><link>https://thefrvrplaylist.com/posts/the-intro-about-nothing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://thefrvrplaylist.com/posts/the-intro-about-nothing/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to thefrvrplaylist! My name is Martin, and for several years now, I have been recording, producing, and engineering my own original music. I felt a strong connection to music around the age of 10, when I began playing the alto saxophone and clarinet in my school band. Music had a special way to uplift my spirits, and a few years later, I began creating my own, originally favoring hip-hop but later finding my lane with R&amp;#x26;B music, which is now my favorite genre.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More recently, I have discovered the passion I have for music is deeper than just creating it. During my free time, when I am not working on my own music, in class achieving my bachelor’s degree in business, at work, where I am a computer repair technician, or working on designing original clothes, I am listening to music. I found that I can talk about music I am into for days, and with the help of my best friend, I decided to create this blog where I will be reviewing new music, showcasing my favorite albums I’m listening to, and just sharing music I like in general. Please feel free to send me recommendations at my email!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Written by Martin Manasherob, who is currently based in the Bay Area. You can &lt;a href=&quot;https://instagram.com/mvrtinfrvr&quot;&gt;connect with him on Instagram&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>